[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In this movie Santa Claus and \u201cCloudy\u201d Russo rough up the punk, demanding to know if he \u201cever picks his feet in Poughkeepsie.\u201d", "correct_answer": "The French Connection", "incorrect_answers": ["Rocky", "The Sting", "The Hustler"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many fluid ounces do 48 quarts equal?", "correct_answer": "1,536", "incorrect_answers": ["1,563", "1,635", "1,653"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is least likely to cause tooth decay according to The American Dental Association?", "correct_answer": "simple sugars", "incorrect_answers": ["potato chips", "breadsticks", "cereals"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Four Corners states of Arizona, Utah, New Mexico and Colorado are all in the same time zone.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the lowlife the two thieves in the beginning of the 1989 movie Batman were talking about on the rooftop?", "correct_answer": "Johnny Gobs", "incorrect_answers": ["Jeremy Givens", "Jeff Gipper", "Jimmy Two-fingers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of meat is used for the preparation of the French dish called Pot-au-feu?", "correct_answer": "Beef", "incorrect_answers": ["Pork", "No meat is used", "Duck"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor won the Academy Award for Best Actor in a Supporting Role at the 81st Academy Awards 2009?", "correct_answer": "Heath Ledger", "incorrect_answers": ["Philip Seymour Hoffman", "Robert Downey Jr.", "Josh Brolin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "General Santa Anna , loser at San Juancinto and victor at the Alamo, went on to help promote what?", "correct_answer": "Chewing gum", "incorrect_answers": ["The Gatling Gun", "Tacos", "Movies"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Light slows down in this object and causes it to look bent.", "correct_answer": "water", "incorrect_answers": ["glass", "lamp", "gas"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How much money was up for grabs in the movie Rat Race?", "correct_answer": "$2,000,000", "incorrect_answers": ["$10,000,000", "$5,000,000", "$1,000,000"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to Dr. Seuss, what goes with ham?", "correct_answer": "Green eggs", "incorrect_answers": ["Orange bacon", "Pink Sausage", "Blue Cheese"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which Wayans brothers teamed up for the 2004 movie White Chicks?", "correct_answer": "Marlon and Shawn", "incorrect_answers": ["Keenen and Dwayne", "Damon and Keenen", "Shawn and Damon"]}]